A Guide to the Hugh L. Robertson Collection, 1948-1983
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Hugh L. Robertson Collection, 1948-1983
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 06-69
2.5 linear feet
The Hugh L. Robertson Collection consists of 2.5 linear feet and spans the years 1948-1983 and contains photographs, negatives, and personal papers. Subjects include the Fairfax County Fire and Rescue Department, Washington D.C., DuMont Television Network, Crane Co., and the Pakistan Embassy.
Robertson, Hugh Lee (1927-2005)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Donated by Ruby L. Robertson in 2008
Historical and Biographical Information
Hugh Lee Robertson was born on February 12, 1927 in Takoma Park, Maryland to Catherine M. and Eppa P. Robertson. After his parents divorced in 1930, his grandmother, Catherine L. Manning, raised him. Manning was philatelic curator of the Smithsonian Institute from 1922 to 1951, the first woman outside the sciences to achieve the rank of Assistant Curator.
Robertson moved to Arlington, Virginia with his grandmother and attended Washington-Lee High School. In 1944, he quit school and joined the Navy as a Fireman First Class (EM striker) and earned the nickname “Rebel”. During World War II he served on tank landing ships in the Pacific arena including the USS Sphinx (LST-963) in 1944 and the USS Orvetta (IX-157) in 1946.
At age 19, he married high school sweetheart Ruby Lee Binsted on October 19, 1946. The couple moved into government housing in Arlington, Virginia. Around the same time, Robertson enrolled as a student at the National School of Photography on 1005 E. Street, N.W. In the early 1950s, Robertson worked as a commercial photographer for Ackad Studios on Connecticut Avenue NW in Washington D.C. He snapped photos of celebrities, politicians, embassy officials, weddings, and even traditional studio portraits for Ackad.
In 1954, the Robertsons moved to 6907 Pine Crest Avenue in McLean, Virginia in the West McLean subdivision. Robertson joined the Fairfax County Fire Department on June 1, 1955 as a Fire Dispatcher, becoming one of its first paid employees. When a person called the emergency number, Robertson answered and dispatched the fire equipment. Simultaneously, Robertson also volunteered with the McLean Volunteer Fire Department. In September 1976, he retired as a Captain.
After retiring, he and his wife volunteered at the McLean Treasure Trove, a consignment shop which benefited Fairfax Hospital. Always an avid collector, Robertson frequently visited yard sales collecting “historical” items. At some point he acquired an original cornerstone from the Fairfax Courthouse (now on display at the Fairfax Museum and Visitors Center) and three of the four original plaques from the long lost four-sided stone marker commemorating the 1863 Battle of Sangster Station (now on display at the Fairfax Station Railroad Museum).
Hugh Robertson died on October 26, 2005.
Scope and Content
Series 1: Personal Papers, 1954-1983
This series contains papers, correspondence, reports, by-laws, newspaper clippings, and periodicals relating to Hugh L. Robertson’s career with the Fairfax County Fire Department. Also included is a press release and a letter from the Embassy of Pakistan granting Robertson press credentials to cover the Prime Minister of Pakistan’s United States visit in 1954.
Series 2: Photographs, 1948-1971
Sub-Series 2-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1957-1971
Robertson took many photographs throughout his career of scenes involving the Fairfax County Fire Department. Included in this series are photographs of fire vehicles from the Bailey’s Crossroads Volunteer Fire Department, Franconia Volunteer Fire Department, Lorton Volunteer Fire Department, McLean Volunteer Fire Department, and the Vienna Volunteer Fire Department as well as the fire board at the Central Fire Control Station. Photos of the groundbreaking of the Reston Fire Station and dedication of the Vienna Fire Station are also included as well as scenes from the Virginia State Firemen’s School. Subjects also include car accidents, crime scenes, fire scenes, and portraits of firefighters. Some of the negatives for these prints may be found in sub-series 3-1.
Sub-Series 2-2: Crane Co., Undated
Crane Co., a plumbing and heating supply firm, opened a new Washington branch location at 10700 Hanna Street in Beltsville, Maryland in 1954. The firm previously operated its Washington branch at 1225 I Street N.W. since the 1920s. The new building had an enclosed warehouse area, offices, display room and was located near a railroad siding. It can be presumed that the photographs in this series are of the newly opened building. Of particular note is that Kahlil Daoud Ackad was the Washington branch manager for Crane Co. from 1950-1959. K.D. Ackad was the brother of Abdon Daoud Ackad, owner of Ackad Studios of which Hugh Robertson photographed for.
Sub-Series 2-3: Washington D.C., Maryland, and Virginia, 1948-c.1950s
Photographs in this series depict scenes from Washington D.C., Maryland or Virginia. Subjects include scenes from the Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America in Washington D.C.; a Chrysler Dealership; the Old Barry Chapel cornerstone in St. Dominic Catholic Church in Washington D.C.; Rock Creek Park; the Noyes Armillary Sphere in Meridian Hill Park; Chapman’s Mill in Broad Run, Virginia; and the “Avenue of Progress” Celebration ribbon cutting of the George Avenue underpass in Silver Spring, Maryland. Also included are a series of photos of a church cornerstone laying service presided over by Archbishop Michael, leader of the Greek Church in North and South America. The Washington D.C. church depicted is either Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Church or St. Sophia Greek Orthodox Church both of which were presided over by Archbishop Michael between 1951 and 1952.
Sub-Series 2-4: Embassy of Pakistan, Washington, D.C., c.1953-1955
In October 1954, when Hugh L. Robertson worked for Ackad Studios, he covered the Prime Minister of Pakistan Mohammad Ali Bograthe’s visit to Washington on behalf of the Pakistan Embassy. Earlier that year in May, he photographed the wedding of Capt. Azhar H. Sadik and Dr. Iffat Nafis Shoaib, daughter of Mohamed Shoaib, the Executive Director of the World Bank, in the Pakistan Embassy. Photographs also included in this series are of a social event at the Pakistan Embassy of which Vice President Richard M. Nixon and his wife, Pat Nixon, attended. Of particular note is the photograph of Richard Nixon smoking a hookah.
Sub-Series 2-5: Dumont Television Network Unknown Television Episode, c. 1950s
Photographs in this series depict the filming of a television episode from an unknown DuMont Television Network series. The show features three Indonesian women dressed in cultural garb. The women interact with the host on set and perform dancing routines. DuMont had a television studio in Washington D.C. and operated locally as WTTG, channel 5.
Sub-Series 2-6: Post-World War II Asia, 1947
During World War II, Hugh L. Robertson served on tank landing ships in the Pacific Arena from 1944-1946. The photographs in this series depict post-war China and Japan. Subjects include Qingdao, China; Tokyo, Japan; Yokosuka, Japan; and Mount Fuji. The photographs are dated 1947 in what appear to be Robertson’s handwriting. The U.S. Navy discharged Robertson in 1946, so it is possible that these photographs are misdated or not even photographed by Robertson himself.
Sub-Series 2-7: Unidentified, Undated
Photographs in this series are unidentified and feature portraits, houses, weddings, social events, and scenery. These photographs were taken by Robertson while he was in photography school and later working for Ackad Studios.
Series 3: Negatives, 1948-1959
Sub-Series 3-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1954-1959
Robertson took many photographs throughout his career of scenes within the Fairfax County Fire Department. The negatives in this series depict scenes involving the Annandale Volunteer Fire Department, Burke Volunteer Fire Department, Dunn Loring Volunteer Fire Department, Fairfax Volunteer Fire Department, Vienna Volunteer Fire Department, Herndon Volunteer Fire Department, Jefferson Volunteer Fire Department, Lorton Volunteer Fire Department, McLean Volunteer Fire Department, and Central Fire Control Station. Subjects of particular interest include the controlled burn of Ossian Hall; billboard signage of the McLean Carnival which was hosted by the McLean VFD; the dedication of the Vienna Fire Station; a wedding of a firefighter at Saint John’s Episcopal Church in Centreville, Virginia; the Washington D.C. Fire Prevention Parade of which the Fairfax County Fire Department participated; and a barn fire which may have been J. Preston Rogers’ McLean, Virginia barn that burned on October 27, 1954. Subjects also include car accidents, crime scenes, fire scenes, and portraits of firefighters. Some of the negatives in this collection have their accompanying prints in sub-series 2-1.
Sub-Series 3-2: Washington D.C., Maryland, and Virginia, 1948, Undated
Negatives in this series depict scenes from Washington D.C., Maryland or Virginia. Subjects include scenes from Great Falls Park; the Noyes Armillary Sphere at Meridian Hill Park; an unknown masonic lodge in Fairfax County; and scenes from the September 11, 1948 “Avenue of Progress” Celebration of the George Avenue underpass dedication in Silver Spring, Maryland.
Sub-Series 3-3: Family Life, c. 1959, Undated
These negatives depict scenes from Hugh L. Robertson’s family life at home at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue in McLean, Virginia. Also included are snow scenes of Dead Run Stream which ran near Robertson’s house and two separate portraits of him.
Sub-Series 3-4: Post-World War II Asia, Undated
The negatives in this series were presumably taken just after World War II by Hugh L. Robertson while serving on a tank landing ship in the Pacific Arena. The subjects are street scenes in an unidentified location in Japan.
Sub-Series 3-5: Unidentified, 1956, Undated
Negatives in this series are unidentified and feature portraits, social events, a farm, a church, and a storefront. These photographs were taken by Robertson while he was in photography school and later while working for Ackad Studios.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
The Catherine Manning Papers and Documents, Smithsonian National Postal Museum
Historic non-Fairfax County documents that Robertson collected on his yard sale excursions were donated to the proper repositories
Index Terms
Crane Co.; Fairfax County (Va.) Fire and Rescue Department; Fire departments - Virginia - Fairfax County; Du Mont Television Network; Lorton (Va.); McLean (Va.); Pakistan. Embassy (U.S.); Qingdao (China); Robertson, Hugh Lee (1927-2005); Washington (D.C.)
Container List
- Series 1: Personal Papers, 1954-1983
  - Letter, Embassy of Pakistan giving Hugh L. Robertson press credentials to cover the Prime Minister's visit, 1954 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press Release, "Pakistan Prime Minister to Lay Wreath", 1954 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Postcard notice, "He Night" annual celebration January 15, 1955 McLean Volunteer Fire Department, 1955 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Resolution, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors on volunteer fire departments, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Department of Corrections Certificate of Appreciation to Delford H. Walthall Jr., Lorton Co. 19 for aid in the Auditorium fire at Lorton Prison on October 30, 1957, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rules for Fairfax County Volunteer Firemen's Association Field Day Contests held September 27, 1958 Annandale, Va., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Program and map, Third Annual Virginia Firemen's School, Williamsburg, Va., 1958 June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, "Operation Checkerboard", Chantilly fire station, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Check stubs, Department of Conservation and Development payment to Delford H Walthall Jr and S. Walthall for forest fire control and forestry services, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from Robert J. Gagnon of the Virginia State Firemen's Association, contains Ashland Fire Department patch, 1963 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Booklet, "Your Retirement From Fairfax County Service", 1963 November (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Wagon Pipe" First Issue, Friendship Fire Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Fairfax County Fire Services Field Incident Coding Manual", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Report, "An Analysis of Fire and Rescue Services in Fairfax County, Preliminary report of the Board of Supervisors Fire Study Sub-committee June 1970", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Vienna Volunteer Fire Department, Re: Fairfax County volunteer fire departments face extinction by Board of Supervisors, 1970 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from Martha V. Pennino, Re: Rebuttal to letter from Vienna Volunteer Fire Department concerning extinction of volunteer fire departments, 1970 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Postcard, Charleston's Medical Complex, South Carolina from "Jay", 1974 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Layout" Official Publication for Fairfax County's Professional Firefighters Vol. IV No. 2, 1983 May (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Brochure, The Friendship Veterans Fire Engine Company, Alexandria, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - List, "Requirements to Train In Emergency Rooms of Local Hospitals" by William E. Brown, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - By-Laws of the Fairfax County Paid Firemen's Association, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Names and Addresses of Fire Departments in Fairfax County, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Job description, Dispatcher I, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Series 2: Photographs, 1948-1971
  - Sub-series 2-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1957-1971
    - 9mm Steyer automatic pistol similar to the gun used in the murder of Percy Sims on February 6, 1958, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Baileys Crossroads VFD floral wreath, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bailey's Crossroads VFD ladder truck outside Mount Vernon-Lee Community building, 1958 June (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Bailey's Crossroads VFD ladder truck outside Mount Vernon-Lee Community building, 1958 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Baileys Crossroads VFD Oren Fire Truck in front of fire department, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Central Fire Control Station and three unidentified men [4 photos], Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337 [2 photos], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Claude Shoop (1930-1973) Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Crestwood Home Demonstration Club (Springfield, Va) exhibit table on American National Red Cross First Aid [2 photos], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, view of the crime scene, c. 1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, view of the crime scene, c. 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Franconia VFD American LaFrance Fire Truck wreck, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Franconia VFD American LaFrance Fire Truck wreck, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Franconia VFD American LaFrance Fire Truck wreck (Franconia Hardware in background), Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Franconia VFD and Penn-Daw Rescue Squad at the scene of a fire [2 photos], 1958 June (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Kensington VFD fire truck with man dangling from extended ladder, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Lorton VFD 1939 American LaFrance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Lorton VFD 1941 Chevrolet 500 GPM Pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Lorton VFD 1941 Chevrolet 500 GPM Pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Lorton VFD 1941 Chevrolet 500 GPM Pumper [2 photos], Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Lorton VFD 1951 Cadillac and 1957 Chevrolet in front of fire station, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Lorton VFD 1951 Cadillac Rescue Squad (interior view) loaned by Civil Defense, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Lorton VFD 1951 Cadillac Rescue Squad loaned by Civil Defense [2 photos], Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Lorton VFD 1951 Cadillac Rescue Squad loaned by Civil Defense, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Lorton VFD 1951 Cadillac Rescue Squad loaned by Civil Defense, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper [2 photos], Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Lorton VFD 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1939 American LaFrance, and 1941 Chevrolet 500 GPM pumper in front of fire station, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Lorton VFD 1957 Chevrolet Rescue Squad donated by Aero Auto [2 photos], Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Lorton VFD 1957 Chevrolet Rescue Squad donated by Aero Auto, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Lorton VFD 1957 Chevrolet Rescue Squad donated by Aero Auto, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Lorton VFD American LaFrance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Lorton VFD Cadillac Ambulance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Lorton VFD Cadillac Ambulance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Lorton VFD Carl Baker Residence Fire, 1958 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Lorton VFD Carl Baker Residence Fire, 1958 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Lorton VFD Chevrolet Ambulance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, fire trucks and crowd gathered [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, house in flames, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, house on fire, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, house on fire, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, house on fire, 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, house post-fire in ruins [2 photos], 1958 April (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old dilapidated house [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Lorton VFD controlled burn, old house burning with firefighter running alongside, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Lorton VFD fire hose stretching to fire truck in the distance, 1958 May (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Lorton VFD fire truck, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Lorton VFD fire truck and other fire apparatus on the scene, 1958 June (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lorton VFD firefighters digging out 1941 Chevrolet pumper stuck in snow, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Lorton VFD firefighters digging out 1941 Chevrolet pumper stuck in snow, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Lorton VFD firefighters on the scene near railroad [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Lorton VFD French Ball "Frenchie" posing next to fire truck, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Lorton VFD French Ball and unidentified firefighter posing next to fire truck, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Lorton VFD front exterior with equipment lined in front, l to r: 1956 FWD 750 GPM pumper, 1939 American LaFrance, 1941 Chevrolet 500 GPM pumper, 1951 Cadillac, 1957 Chevrolet [2 photos], Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Lorton VFD rescue squad boat piloted by two men under Occoquan Bridge, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Lorton VFD smoldering ruins after a fire, 1958 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Lorton VFD truck accident, tractor trailer being towed by "Big Moe" truck [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Lorton VFD truck accident, tractor trailer wreckage [2 photos], 1958 May (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Lorton VFD truck accident, tractor trailer wreckage, 1958 May (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Lorton VFD unidentified firefighter posing next to fire truck, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters gathered around the wreck, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - McLean VFD car accident, front close-up of wrecked Mercury, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - McLean VFD car accident, overturned log truck and wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - McLean VFD car accident, overturned log truck and wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - McLean VFD car accident, side close-up of wrecked Mercury, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - McLean VFD car accident, underside view of overturned log truck, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - McLean VFD crew on firetruck in downtown McLean, Peoples Drug in background, identified are Mac, Kenny, Ray, and Hugh L. Robertson,, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - McLean VFD crew on firetruck, identified are Hugh L. Robertson and Kenny, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - McLean VFD firefighters out of gear using a ladder to climb a building, identified are Mac, Kenny, and Hugh L. Robertson, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - McLean VFD four fire apparatus, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Reston Fire Station Co. 25 groundbreaking L to R: George Alexander, William H. Magness (Gulf Reston President), Martha V. Pennino, Norman Bradford, G. Truman Ward and Charles E. Hall., 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Reston Fire Station Co. 25 groundbreaking L to R: George Alexander, William H. Magness (Gulf Reston President), Martha V. Pennino, Norman Bradford, G. Truman Ward and Charles E. Hall., 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Dewitt Crickenberger showing award to unidentified group, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters shaking hands in front of cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, floral arrangements inside bay door, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, furniture and television set donated by Miller & Wren Furniture Co, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, furniture donated by Miller & Wren Furniture Co, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of firefighters posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 37)